[BUY A BAG OF ICE BREAKER AND GET ONE FREE WITH CODE 'POWERPLAY.' SHOP NOW](https://www.deathwishcoffee.com/products/ice-breaker-coffee?variant=40882657132599)

[TODAY ONLY: ENTER FOR A CHANCE TO WIN A FROSTBITE GOLDEN TICKET MUG](https://www.deathwishcoffee.com/blogs/lifestyle/how-to-get-your-mittens-on-the-frostbite-golden-ticket-mug)

* Coffee
    
    Coffee

* Merch
    
    Merch

    * 

    * 

[Log in](https://www.deathwishcoffee.com/account/login) Search [Cart](https://www.deathwishcoffee.com/cart)

Item added to your cart
-----------------------

Check out

Continue shopping

Access Denied

**IMPORTANT!** If you’re a store owner, please make sure you have [Customer accounts enabled in your Store Admin](https://admin.shopify.com/store//settings/checkout), as you have customer based locks set up with EasyLockdown app. [Enable Customer Accounts](https://admin.shopify.com/store//settings/checkout)

Death Wish Coffee Company - Privacy Policy
==========================================

PRIVACY STATEMENT  
  
\----  
  
SECTION 1 - WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?  
  
When you purchase something from our store, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address, phone number, and email address.  
When you browse our store, we also automatically receive your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system to give you the best experience possible.  
Email marketing: With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products, and other updates.

We will never supply any of your information to a third party.

Text marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send text messages about our store, new products, and other updates. Updates include Checkout Reminders. Webhooks will be used to trigger the Checkout Reminders messaging system.

SECTION 2 - CONSENT  
  
**How do you get my consent?**  
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, contact our helpdesk, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, you then give consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.  
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent or provide you with an opportunity to say no.  
  
**How do I withdraw my consent?**  
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at any time, by contacting us at hq@deathwishcoffee.com or by mailing us at:  
Death Wish Coffee Company  
260 Broadway, Saratoga Springs, NY 12866  
  
SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE  
  
We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.  
  
SECTION 4 - SHOPIFY  
  
Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.  
Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases, and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.  
  
Payment:  
If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.  
All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.  
PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.  
For more insight, you may also want to read Shopify’s Terms of Service here or Privacy Statement here.  
  
SECTION 5 - THIRD-PARTY SERVICES  
  
In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.  
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.  
We have worked closely with our processors to be sure of full compliance and have confirmed this with all of our current processors.   
In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located in a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.  
As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.  
Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.  
  
Links  
When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites and encourage you to read their privacy statements.  
SECTION 6 - SECURITY  
  
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.  
If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.  
  
SECTION 7 - COOKIES  
  
Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.  
\_session\_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc.).  
\_shopify\_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits  
\_shopify\_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.  
cart, unique token, persistent for two weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.  
\_secure\_session\_id, unique token, sessional  
storefront\_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.  
n  
SECTION 8 - AGE OF CONSENT  
  
By using this site, you represent that you are at least the age of majority in your state or province of residence, or that you are the age of majority in your state or province of residence and you have given us your consent to allow any of your minor dependents to use this site.  
  
SECTION 9 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  
  
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.  
If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.  
  
QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION  
  
If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at hey@deathwishcoffee.com or by mail at  
Death Wish Coffee Company  
\[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer\]  
260 Broadway, Saratoga Springs, NY 12866

\----

Invalid password

 [Enter](javascript:void(0);)

LET'S DRINK COFFEE AND THROW THINGS AT HAPPY PEOPLE
---------------------------------------------------

End of the road, jack.
----------------------

Company
-------

Accounts + Orders
-----------------

Legal
-----

GET WIRED WITH US
-----------------

© 2024, [Death Wish Coffee](https://www.deathwishcoffee.com/ "Death Wish Coffee"). All rights reserved.

GET WIRED WITH US
-----------------

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
* Opens in a new window.
